Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Bio Files, 1919-2015; 390.66 Linear feet (391 boxes)
  - -K-
    - Kravchenko, Victor, 1946-1966 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 10)
    - Kreeger, David Lloyd, 1961-1990 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 11)
    - Kreisky, Bruno, 1959-1990 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 12)
    - Kreisler, Fritz, 1925-1991 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 13-14)
    - Kreuger, Ivar, 1938-1968 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 15)
    - Krock, Arthur, 1932-1979 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 16)
    - Kroger, Peter and Helen, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 17)
    - Krueger, Walter, 1941-1967 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 18)
    - Krupskaya, Nadezhda, 1929-1967 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 19)
    - Kubelik, Rafael, 1941-1983 (Offsite-box 1467, Folder 20)
    - Kubitschek, Juscelino, 1951-1976 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 1-4)
    - Kuchel, Thomas Henry, 1956-1963 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 5)
    - Kudirka, Simas, 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 1558, Folder 6)
    - Kueng, Hans, 1953-1993 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 6)
    - Kuhn, Allan Dale, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 7)
    - Kuhn, Walt, 1934-1989 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 8-9)
    - Kuiper, Gerard Peter, 1940-1992 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 10)
    - Kunstler, William M., 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 11)
    - Kurusu, Saburo, 1941-1968 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 12)
    - Kuter, Laurence Sherman, 1942-1979 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 13)
    - Kuznetsov, Anatoly, 1967-1985 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 14)
  - -L-
    - LaBouisse, Henry Richardson, Jr., 1935-1987 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 15-17)
    - Lader, Lawrence, 1955-1992 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 18)
    - Laderman, Ezra, 1955-1990 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 19)
    - La Farge, John, 1937-1988 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 20)
    - La Follette, Robert Marion, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 1468, Folder 21)
    - La Follette, Robert Marion, Jr., 1923-1970 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 1)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello H., 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 2-9)
    - Laing, Ronald David, 1969-1989 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 10)
    - Laird, Melvin R., 1962-1988 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 11-13)
    - Lalique, Rene, 1932-1980 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 14)
    - Lamaze, Fernand, 1964-1980 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 15)
    - Lamb, Charles and Mary, 1936-1980 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 16)
    - Lamm, Richard D., 1973-1985 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 17)
    - Landon, Alfred Mossman, 1935-1991 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 18-20)
    - Lang, George E., 1961-1986 (Offsite-box 1469, Folder 21)
    - Lang, Jack, 1982-1989 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 1)
    - Langlie, Arthur Bernard, 1956-1968 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 2)
    - Langmuir, Irving, 1929-1987 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 3)
    - Lanksy, Meyer, 1957-1990 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 4)
    - Lapham, Roger Dearborn, 1937-1966 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 5)
    - Laporte, Pierre, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 6)
    - Lara, Agustin, 1938-1991 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 7)
    - Laragh, John Henry, 1960-1991 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 8)
    - Larkin, Philip, 1958-1993 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 9)
    - La Rouche, Lyndon Hermyle, Jr., 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 10)
    - Larson, Leonard W., 1961-1974 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 11-12)
    - Lasagna, Louis, 1964-1990 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 13)
    - Lasansky, Mauricio, 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 14)
    - Lasker, Mary Woodward, 1948-1980 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 15)
    - Lattimore, Owen, 1958-1992 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 16)
    - Laubach, Frank Charles, 1939-1986 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 17)
    - Lauder family, 1973-1986 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 18)
    - Laurel, Salvador, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1470, Folder 19)
    - Lausche, Frank J., 1941-1972 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 1-2)
    - Lawrence, Ernest Orlando, 1937-1990 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 3)
    - Lawrence, Jacob, 1943-1994 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 4)
    - Lawrence, Thomas Edward, 1926-1992 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 5-7)
    - Lawson, John Howard, 1939-1980 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 8)
    - Laxalt, Paul, 1964 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 9)
    - Layton, Larry, 1978-1987 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 10)
    - Le, Duc Tho, 1972-1992 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 11)
    - Leacock, Stephen, 1935-1992 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 12)
    - Leader, George M., 1954-1972 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 13)
    - Leahy, Patrick J., 1974-1986 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 14)
    - Leahy, William D., 1936-1959 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 15)
    - Leakey family, 1964-1993 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 16)
    - Leakey, Louis S. B., 1958-1990 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 17)
    - Lear, Edward, 1948-1990 (Offsite-box 1471, Folder 18)
    - Lear, Martha Weiman, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 1)
    - Leavis, Frank Raymond, 1947-1986 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 2)
    - Leavitt, David, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 3)
    - Le Boyer, Frederick, 1975-1989 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 4)
    - LeBrun, Rico, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 5)
    - Ledeen, Michael A., 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 6)
    - Lederberg, Joshua, 1957-1978 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 7)
    - Lederer, William J., 1958-1965 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 8)
    - Lederman, Leon M., 1965-1989 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 9)
    - Leduc, Violette, 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 10)
    - Lee, Andrew Daulton, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 11)
    - Lee, Burton J., III, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 12)
    - Lee, Doris, 1937-1991 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 13)
    - Lee, Dorothy McCullough, 1948-1961 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 14)
    - Lee, Ivy, 1924-1967 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 15)
    - Lee, Kuan Yew, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 16-17)
    - Lee, Richard C., 1956-1967 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 18)
    - Lee, Robert Edward, 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 1472, Folder 19-20)
    - Lee, Robert Edward, 1930-1962 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 1-4)
    - Lee, Tsung Dao, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 5)
    - Lefkowitz, Louis J., 1956-1984 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 6)
    - Leger, Alexis, 1950-1987 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 7)
    - Legge, Walter, 1952-1984 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 8)
    - Legman, Gershon, 1955-1967 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 9)
    - Legros, Fernand, 1967-1983 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 10)
    - Lehder, Carlos Enrique, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 11)
    - Lehman family, 1948-1989 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 12)
    - Lehman, Herbert Henry, 1934-1987 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 13)
    - Lehman, John F., Jr., 1976-1987 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 14)
    - Lehman, Robert, 1966-1990 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 15)
    - Lehmann-Haupt, Christopher, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 16)
    - Lei, Feng, 1963-1990 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 17)
    - Leigh, Gustavo, 1973-1990 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 18)
    - Leighton, Robert B., 1958-1968 (Offsite-box 1473, Folder 19)
    - Leinsdorf, Erich, 1947-1993 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 1)
    - LeJeune, Jerome J.L.M., 1960-1994 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 2)
    - Leland, Henry Martyn, 1931-1989 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 3)
    - Lem, Stanislaw, 1970-1984 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 4)
    - Lemass, Sean F., 1959-1977 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 5-7)
    - Le May, Curtis Emerson, 1944-1990 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 8-12)
    - Lemnitzer, Lyman L., 1942-1975 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 13-15)
    - L'Enfant, Pierre Charles, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 16)
    - Lengyel, Margaret, 1973 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 17)
    - Lenin, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 1502, Folder 18-23)
    - Lenin, 1929-1969 (Offsite-box 1503, Folder 1-15)
    - Lenz, Widukind, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 1503, Folder 16)
    - Leo XIII, Pope, 1941-1968 (Offsite-box 1503, Folder 17)
    - Leonard, John, 1968-1980 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 1)
    - Leonov, Aleksei Arkhipovich, 1965-1975 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 2)
    - Leonowens, Anna, 1946-1980 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 3)
    - Leontief, Wassily W., 1964-1992 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 4)
    - Le Pen, Jean-Marie, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 5)
    - Lerner, Max, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 6)
    - Lescaze, William E., 1937-1991 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 7)
    - Leslie, Alfred, 1952-1992 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 8)
    - Lester, Richard Allen, 1960-1977 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 9)
    - Letelier, Orlando, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 10-11)
    - Leuchtenburg, William E., 1958-1979 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 12)
    - Leutwiler, Fritz, 1973-1987 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 13)
    - Levchenko, Stanislav A., 1979-1989 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 14)
    - Leventhal, Nathan, 1972-1984 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 15)
    - Lever, Norman Harold, 1952-1990 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 16)
    - Levesque, Rene, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 1504, Folder 17)
    - Levi, Carlo, 1946-1989 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 1)
    - Levi, Edward H., 1959-1987 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 2)
    - Levi, Primo, 1959-1988 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 3)
    - Levich, Veniamin G., 1972-1987 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 4)
    - Levi-Montalcini, Rita, 1960-1988 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 5)
    - Levin, Meyer, 1959-1988 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Jack, 1950-1987 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 7)
    - Levine, Les, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 8)
    - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1961-1978 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 9)
    - Levitt, Abraham, 1955-1962 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 10)
    - Levitt, Alfred S., 1950-1966 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 11)
    - Levitt, Arthur J., 1954-1988 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 12)
    - Levitt, I.M., 1954-1969 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 13)
    - Levitt, William J., 1950-1987 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 14)
    - Levy, Marvin David, 1955-1987 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 15)
    - Lewis, Ann F., 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 16)
    - Lewis, Anthony, 1955-1980 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 17)
    - Lewis, David, 1971-1981 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 18)
    - Lewis, John Henry, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 19)
    - Lewis, Oscar, 1960-1977 (Offsite-box 1505, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Reginald F., 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Samuel W., 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Stephen, 19770-1990 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Wyndham Percy, 1932-1987 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 4)
    - Lewis and Clark, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 5-6)
    - Lew, Willy, 1951-1969 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 7)
    - Li, Choh Hao, 1949-1983 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 8)
    - Li, Fu-Chun, 1961-1975 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 9-10)
    - Li, Peng, 1985-1993 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 11)
    - Libby, Willard F., 1955-1989 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 12-13)
    - Liberman, Yevsey G., 1965-1988 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 14-15)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 16)
    - Liddell Hart, Basil Henry, 1940-1979 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 17)
    - Liddy, George Gordon, 1973-1986 (Offsite-box 1506, Folder 18)
    - Lie, Trygve, 1944-1987 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 1-2)
    - Liebling, Abbott Joseph, 1964-1992 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 3)
    - Lifton, Robert Jay, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 4)
    - Ligeti, Gyorgy, 1965-1990 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 5)
    - Lightner, Candy, 1984-1990 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 6)
    - Lillehei, Clarence Walton, 1954-1979 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 7)
    - Lilly, John C., 1950-1990 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 8)
    - Lin, Biao, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 9)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1507, Folder 10-15)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 1)
    - Lindsay, Mary, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 2)
    - Liotta, Domingo, 1966-1972 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 3)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1947-1991 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 4)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1932-1989 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 5-8)
    - Listz, Franz, 1934-1989 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 9-12)
    - Little, Royal, 1946-1989 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 13)
    - Litvinoff, Maxim, 1933-1985 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 14)
    - Liu, Shaoqi, 1949-1980 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 15-17)
    - Liuzzo, Viola Gregg, 1966-1983 (Offsite-box 1508, Folder 18)
    - Lloyd, Frank, 1973-1982 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 1)
    - Lo, Jui-Ching, 1956-1979 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 2-3)
    - Lodge, George Cabot, II, 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 4)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1936-1985 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 5-9)
    - Loewy, Raymond Fernand, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 10-11)
    - Logue, Edward J., 1956-1976 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 12)
    - Long, Earl Kemp, 1939-1984 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 13-14)
    - Long, Huey Pierce, 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 1509, Folder 15)
    - Long, Huey Piece, 1928-1985 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 1-3)
    - Long, Russell B., 1948-1986 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 4-5)
    - Lonsdale, Gordon Arnold, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 6)
    - Lopez, Adolfo, 1957-1970 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 7-9)
    - Lopez, Jose, 1976-1983 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 10-12)
    - Lord, Bette, 1962-1988 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 13)
    - Lorenz, Konrad, 1962-1989 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 14)
    - Lothian, Eleventh Marquess of, 1930-1960 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 15)
    - Lott, Trent, 1982-1988 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 16)
    - Loudon, John H., 1958-1965 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 17-19)
    - Lougheed, Peter, 1974-1980 (Offsite-box 1510, Folder 20)
    - Louis, Morris, 1957-1992 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 1-2)
    - Lovelock, James E., 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 3)
    - Loving, Mildred, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 4)
    - Loving, Richard Perry, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 5)
    - Low, David, 1936-1975 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 6)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1967-1986 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 7)
    - Lowenstein, Allard K., 1968-1992 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 8)
    - Lowry, Malcolm, 1947-1989 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 9)
    - Lucas, Henry Lee, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 10)
    - Luchese, Rhomas, 1947-1979 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 11)
    - Lucy, Autherine J., 1955-1963 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 13)
    - Ludendorff, Erich Friedrick Wilheim, 1930-1985 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 14)
    - Lumumba, Patrice, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 1511, Folder 15-18)
    - Lumumba, Patrice, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 1512, Folder 1-5)
    - Luther, Martin, 1959-1990 (Offsite-box 1512, Folder 6-13)
    - Luther, Martin, 1930-1958 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 1)
    - Lutoslawksi, Witold, 1953-1989 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 2)
    - Luxemburg, Rosa, 1963-1983 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 3)
    - Lysekno, Trofim Denisovich, 1953-1981 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 4)
    - Lytton, Bart, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 5)
  - -M-
    - Mabus, Ray, Jr., 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 6)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, 1951-1993 (Offsite-box 1513, Folder 7-14)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, 1930-1942 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 1)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, II, 1946-1967 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 2)
    - MacDonald, John Dann, 1969-1988 (Offsite-box 1922, Folder 11-12)
    - MacDonald, Peter, Sr., 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 1922, Folder 13)
    - MacDowell, Edward Alexander, 1930-1991 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 3)
    - MacFadden, Bernarr, 1932-1963 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 4)
    - Maciavelli, Niccolo, 1950-1993 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 5)
    - Mackenzie, Compton, 1938-1972 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 6)
    - Mackintosh, Charles Rennie, 1953-1989 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 7)
    - Mackle, Elliot, Frank and Robert, 1956-1965 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 8)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1950-1982 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 9)
    - Macklowe, Harry, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 10)
    - MacLean, Fitzroy Hew, 1944-1987 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 11)
    - MacMillan family, 1960-1992 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 12)
    - MacMillan, Donald B., 1937-1970 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 13)
    - MacMillan, Harold, 1966-1987 (Offsite-box 1514, Folder 14-15)
    - MacMillan, Harold, 1943-1965 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 1-4)
    - MacNelly, Jeffrey K., 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 5)
    - Maddox, Lester Garfield, 1966-1973 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 6)
    - Magliore, Paul, 1946-1988 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 7)
    - Magnuson, Warren G., 1943-1989 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 8)
    - Magritte, Rene, 1947-1992 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 9)
    - Magruder, Jeb Stuart, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 10)
    - Magsaysay, Ramon, 1951-1986 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 11-12)
    - Maheu, Robert A., 1973-1977 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 13)
    - Mahfouz, Naguib, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 14)
    - Mahler, Gustav, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1515, Folder 15-18)
    - Mahler, Gustav, 1930-1964 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 1-2)
    - Mahoney, David J., 1952-1983 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 3)
    - Mahoney, Roger M., 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 4)
    - Mai, Van Bo, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 5)
    - Maidman, Irving, 1955-1979 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 6)
    - Mailer family, 1960-1983 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 7)
    - Maillol, Aristide, 1944-1990 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 8)
    - Major, John, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 9)
    - Makarios III, Archbishop, 1952-1986 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 10)
    - Malamud, Bernard, 1957-1989 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 11)
    - Malek, Frederic V., 1972-1991 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 12)
    - Malendkov, Georgi M., 1938-1988 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 13-16)
    - Malevich, Kasimir, 1970-1991 (Offsite-box 1516, Folder 17)
    - Malfitano, Catherine, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 1)
    - Malik, Jacob A., 1950-1984 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 2)
    - Malinovsky, Rodion Y., 1943-1984 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 3)
    - Mallarme, Stephane, 1936-1989 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 4)
    - Malone, Dumas, 1943-1987 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 5)
    - Malraux, Andre, 1936-1986 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 6-9)
    - Mandel, Marvin, 1969-1987 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 10)
    - Mandela, Nelson R., 1964-1991 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 11-12)
    - Mandela, Winnie, 1977-1963 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 13)
    - Mandelstam, Nadezhda, 1961-1980 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 14)
    - Mandelstam, Osip, 1967-1990 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 15)
    - Manet, Edouard, 1929-1993 (Offsite-box 1517, Folder 16-17)
    - Manley, Michael, 1972-1992 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 1)
    - Mann, Horace, 1936-1991 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 2)
    - Mann, William D'Alton, 1960-1992 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 3)
    - Manning, Robert J., 1964-1980 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 4)
    - Mannerheim, Carl Gustaf Emil, 1934-1974 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 5-6)
    - Manning, Harry, 1932-1974 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 7)
    - Mano, D. Keith, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 8)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1944-1988 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 9-12)
    - Mao, Zedong, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 1518, Folder 13-16)
    - Mao, Zedong, 1962-1980 (Offsite-box 1519)
    - Mao, Zedong, 1936-1961 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 1-4)
    - Marcello, Carlos, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 5)
    - Marchais, Georges, 1978-1988 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 6)
    - Marchetti, Victor L., 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 7)
    - Marchi, John J., 1967-1975 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 8)
    - Marcinkus, Paul, 1979-1990 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 9)
    - Marconi, Guglielmo, 1951-1989 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 10)
    - Marcos, Ferdinand E., 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1520, Folder 11-14)
    - Marcos, Ferdinand E., 1966 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 1-2)
    - Marcos, Imelda Romualdez, 1966-1991 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 3-4)
    - Marin, John, 1949-1991 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 5-6)
    - Marin, Luis, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 7)
    - Marino, Eugene A., 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 8)
    - Marisol, 1962-1975 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 9)
    - Market, Lester, 1949-1977 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 10)
    - Markov, Georgi, 1978-1991 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 11)
    - Marks, Paul S., 1967-1988 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 12)
    - Marmor, Judd, 1965-1989 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 13)
    - Marrakesh, Pasha of, 1951-1986 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 14)
    - Marquand, John Phillips, 1938-1988 (Offsite-box 1521, Folder 15-17)
    - Marriner, Neville, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 1554, Folder 1)
    - Marsh, Stanley, III, 1974-1986 (Offsite-box 1554, Folder 2)
    - Marshall, George Catlett, 1938-1993 (Offsite-box 1554, Folder 3-13)
    - Marshall, John, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 1554, Folder 14-16)
    - Marshall, Thurgood, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 1-2)
    - Marti, Jose Julien, 1936-1991 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Edward, 1930-1967 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 4)
    - Martin, Glenn Luther, 1933-1963 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Joseph William, Jr., 1938-1968 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 6)
    - Martin, William McChesney, Jr., 1938-1979 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 7-9)
    - Martinez, Eugenio R., 1972-1987 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 10)
    - Martinez, Ilich, 1975-1991 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 11)
    - Marx, Karl, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1559, Folder 12-15)
    - Marx, Karl, 1931-1972 (Offsite-box 1560, Folder 1-8)
    - Marx, Louis, 1945-1982 (Offsite-box 1560, Folder 9-10)
    - Marx, Robert F., 1955-1983 (Offsite-box 1560, Folder 11)
    - Mary, Queen of Scots, 1930-1987 (Offsite-box 1560, Folder 12)
    - Mary, Virgin, 1964-1993 (Offsite-box 1560, Folder 13-17)
    - Mary, Virgin, 1931-1963 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 1-6)
    - Masaryk, Jan, 1943-1992 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 7-9)
    - Masaryk, Thomas Garrigue, 1937-1991 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 10-11)
    - Masefield, John, 1930-1987 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 12)
    - Masina, Giuleitta, 1963-1994 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 13)
    - Maslow, Abraham, 1960-1986 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 14)
    - Masseli, Nathan, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 15)
    - Massie, Robert K., 1974-1989 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 16)
    - Masson, Andre, 1963-1987 (Offsite-box 1561, Folder 17)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1932-1983 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 1)
    - Mathias, Charles McCurdy, Jr., 1967-1988 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 2)
    - Matlovich, Leonard Philip, 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 3-4)
    - Matsuoka, Yosuke, 1940-1946 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 5)
    - Matsushita, Konosuke, 1958-1989 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 6-8)
    - Matta, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 9)
    - Matthews, Herbert Lionel, 1943-1975 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 10)
    - Matthiessen, Peter, 1967-1991 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 11)
    - Mauldin, Bill, 1944-1978 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 12-14)
    - Mauriac, Francois, 1930-1988 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 15)
    - Maurois, Andre, 1927-1987 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 16)
    - Mauroy, Peirre, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1562, Folder 17)
    - May, Rollo, 1959-1981 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 1)
    - Mayakovsky, Vladimir, 1930-1991 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 2)
    - Mayle, Peter, 1976-1991 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 3)
    - Maynard, Joyce, 1967-1987 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 4)
    - Mayo, Charles Horace and William James, 1936-1964 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 5)
    - Mayo, Charles Horace, 1930-1982 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 6)
    - Mayo, Charles William, 1934-1984 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 7)
    - Mayo, William James, 1930-1984 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 8)
    - Mazurov, Kiril T., 1965-1989 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 9)
    - Mbeki, Govan, 1986-1990 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 10)
    - Mbeki, Thabo, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 11)
    - Mboya, Tom, 1955-1990 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 12-14)
    - McAdoo, Eleanor Wilson, 1945-1969 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 15)
    - McAlister, Elizabeth, 1971-1988 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 16)
    - McAuliffe, Anothony Clement, 1948-1985 (Offsite-box 1563, Folder 17)
    - McAuliffe, Christa, 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 1564, Folder 1-2)
    - McCandless, Bruce, II, 1966-1987 (Offsite-box 1564, Folder 3)
    - McCain, John Sidney, III, 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 1564, Folder 4)
    - McCarren, Patrick Anthony, 1948-1990 (Offsite-box 1564, Folder 5)
    - McCarthy, Eugene J., 1958-1991 (Offsite-box 1564, Folder 6-10)